Here's a list of seven bare minimum longevity standards that I personally will try to maintain
forever.
And you should too.
Let's dance in style.
Let's dance for a while.
Heaven can wait.
We're only watching the skies.
Hoping for the best but expecting the worst.
Are you gonna drop the ball all night?
Let us dance in style.
Let's dance in style.
Let's dance for a while.
Heaven can wait.
We're only watching the skies.
Hoping for the best but expecting the worst.
Are you gonna drop the ball all night?
Let us dance in style.
Let us die young or let us live forever.
We don't have the power but we never say never.
Sitting in a sand pit life is a short trip.
The music's for the sad man.
We're ever young.
I wanna be forever young.
Do you really want to live forever?
Forever.
Here's a list of seven bare minimum longevity standards that I personally will try to maintain
forever.
Here's a list of seven bare minimum longevity standards that I personally will try to maintain.